capcom.com 2005-04-19

# Privacy Policy

**

**

**Capcom** **USA** **'s** **Online Privacy Policy**

Capcom USA and its subsidiaries (collectively, "Capcom USA " or "Capcom") respect the privacy rights of our online visitors and are committed to protecting the information collected from you.  To further this commitment, we have adopted an Online Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, use, and disclose the information you provide to Capcom online. 

This Privacy Policy Statement and the certification seal located on this page confirms that Capcom is a valid licensee and participating member in the [Entertainment Software Rating Board's Privacy Online Program: ESRB Privacy Online](http://www.esrb.org/).  To protect your privacy, we have voluntarily undertaken this privacy initiative and all of our websites have been reviewed and certified by ESRB Privacy Online to meet established online information collection and use practices.  As part of this privacy program, we are subject to frequent audits of our sites and other enforcement and accountability mechanisms administered independently by the ESRB. 

Whenever you visit a website that displays the ESRB Privacy Online certification seal, you can expect to be notified of the following:  

·        [The websites and information covered by this Privacy Policy](http://www.capcom.com/#_To_which_websites); 

·        [Exactly what information may be collected and how it will be used](http://www.capcom.com/#_What_types_of); 

·        [The consequences, if any, resulting from your refusal to provide personal information](http://www.capcom.com/#_What_happens_if); 

·        [Whether a company uses cookies, tracks IP addresses, or uses other passive means to collect information](http://www.capcom.com/#_Does_Crave_use); 

·        [Who, if anyone, is collecting your personal information](http://www.capcom.com/#_Who_is_collecting);

·        [With whom, if anyone, is your personal information shared](http://www.capcom.com/#_With_whom_does); 

·        [What is a company's policy regarding links to third party sites](http://www.capcom.com/#_What_is_Crave's); 

·        [What choices you have with regard to the use of your personal information](http://www.capcom.com/#_Can_I_choose); 

·        [How you can access, and if necessary, change the personal information a company collects and maintains](http://www.capcom.com/#_How_can_I); 

·        [Whether and how information is collected from children under 13](http://www.capcom.com/#_Does_Crave_collect); 

·        [How a company ensures data security, quality, and integrity; and](http://www.capcom.com/#_What_safeguards_does), 

·        [Where and how to ask questions or file complaints](http://www.capcom.com/#_How_do_I). 

This Privacy Policy currently applies to the following website operated by Capcom: 

In addition, Capcom may own several other domain names that point to the website listed above.  From time to time, we may add new sites and will take reasonable steps to update the list. 

Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information submitted and collected online through the websites listed above, and does not apply to information that may be collected by Capcom offline.  In addition, this Privacy Policy applies to Capcom USA only, and not to our international affiliates (Capcom Asia, Capcom Europe, and Capcom Japan ).  When you link to these foreign sites or to any other sites from a website operated by Capcom USA (as listed above), this Privacy Policy no longer applies. 

In order to give you the best experience on our sites, Capcom may collect information about you, but only if you voluntarily provide it to us.  Typically, we may ask a user to submit personal and/or demographic information, and it will usually take the form of either: (1) Capcom [registration](http://www.capcom.com/#_Registration); (2) [community forum registration](http://www.capcom.com/#_Product_Support/Customer_Service); (3) purchase of a product or service at our [online store](http://www.capcom.com/#_Online_Store_2);(4) [tell-a-friend feature](http://www.capcom.com/#_Tell); and/or, (5) personal information submitted in a business capacity (e.g., [resumes](http://www.capcom.com/#_Resumes)). The types of information that may be requested for each activity and the way the information may be used are detailed below. 

To register on one of our websites, we may ask you to provide personal information such as your name and email address, and demographic information such as your date of birth.  The information that you submit during registration will be used to: (a) enter your name into our monthly raffles and other promotional giveaways; (b) allow you to participate in certain activities and features offered exclusively to registered users (e.g., game-specific events); and, (c) send you a free subscription to our quarterly newsletter, which will keep you informed about upcoming releases, special new offers, and other events or opportunities that we believe you'd be interested in.  You must be 13 years old or older to register. 

Before you can post messages on our message board, we require that you become a registered user.  Typically, this may involve submitting to us personal information such as your email address and full name, and creating a desired username and password.  We may also request and collect demographic information about you, including your gender, occupation, home page URL, the city, state and country in which you live, and other preferences; and, combine such information with your personal information.  The personal and demographic information that you submit to us during this process will allow you to post messages and will be used to tailor your message board experience to your preferences.  To simply read messages posted on our bulletin board, you do not need to register.  However, you must be at least 13 years old to post or even read any messages. 

The ability to participate in the community forums by simply logging in is available to only those Web users that have already created a password during an earlier visit to the message board registration area of a Capcom USA website. To login as a registered user, we may ask you to submit your username and password. This information is collected so that you can access and participate in the message board without having to reregister. 

Please note that whenever you give out personal information in public areas such as on our community forums, that information can be collected and used by people you don't know.  While we strive to protect those who wish to participate in these forums, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you post in these areas.  When you register to use our message board, you have the option to make your email address inaccessible to other viewers or users of the message board. 

Visitors purchasing goods or services at our online store will need to provide a valid credit card number and expiration date, in addition to name, mailing and billing addresses, phone number and e-mail address. We may also ask you to create a login name and password so that when you return to our website, you can easily retrieve your shopping cart by logging in. 

This feature will allow you to send an e-card or web page from our website to a friend. To make this feature work, we typically ask for your name and e-mail address and the name and e-mail address of the recipient. This information is collected solely for the purpose of forwarding your message to persons you choose and is deleted once the message has been sent. 

## §         _Resumes_

Capcom may provide on its websites an email address that visitors can use to send us their resumes. Personal information collected from resumes will be used for the purpose of accepting and evaluating candidate submissions for job postings and may therefore be shared within our company.  Other than as explained above, this Privacy Policy does not apply to personal information gathered through resumes. 

Unless noted otherwise, we may also use your personal and demographic information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve the products and services we provide you and to better meet your needs. 

No matter what method we use to collect information and no matter how we use that information, we will only collect the information deemed reasonably necessary to fulfill your online requests and our legitimate business objectives. 

If you choose not to submit personal information when requested, you may not be able to participate in certain activities on our websites and may considerably limit the services we can provide you.  For example, if you refuse to provide your email address to us, you will not be able to use our message boards or enter any of our raffles.  To simply use our websites, however, you do not need to give us any personal information. 

_Cookies_

Capcom may use cookies on its websites.  A "cookie" is a small bit of record-keeping information that websites often store on a user's computer. Cookies do not include people's names, e-mail addresses, or other information that is personally identifiable; they are used only to identify the computer.  The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many major websites use them.  You can, however, set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.  To purchase online, however, you must accept cookies. 

_IP Addresses_

We do not keep track of Internet Protocol (IP) addresses.  An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet. __

The information that you disclose while visiting any of our websites is collected by Capcom USA , and is used in the manner specified [above](http://www.capcom.com/#_What_types_of). ****

Capcom may share your personal information with our parent, subsidiary, or affiliate companies for purposes of internal marketing and demographic studies, which help us improve and tailor the products and services we provide you.  

We may also disclose personal information in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, or that doing so is reasonably necessary to comply with legal processes; respond to any claims; or, to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Capcom, our customers, or the public.   

In addition, information about our customers, including personal information, may be disclosed to a third party as part of any bankruptcy, merger, sale, transfer of company assets, acquisition, or similar event.  We will require any such third party to agree to maintain the confidentiality, security, and integrity of any personal information transferred or shared for this purpose. 

You should be aware that while you are on a website operated by Capcom, you may be directed to other sites that are beyond our control and for which we are not responsible.  Because we cannot guarantee that the privacy policies of these websites meet our high standards and the requirements of the ESRB Privacy Online Program, we recommend that you read the privacy policy of the website to which you link before you submit any personal information.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter or information about our products and services, you can opt-out from receiving such communications by selecting the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the newsletter email or by sending a remove request to [megamail@capcom.com](mailto:megamail@capcom.com).  Alternatively, you may call us at (408) 774-0400.  We will be happy to honor your request. 

If you have registered to use the message board on one of our sites and wish to update your profile, you may do so online by clicking on "Create/Edit Profile" from the Capcom Community section of the website at which you registered.  You may be required to submit your login name and password before you can access and/or update your profile. 

If you wish to review, update, or delete any other personal information that we may have collected about you, please contact us by phone at (408) 774-0400, via email at [megamail@capcom.com](mailto:megamail@capcom.com), or by regular mail at: Customer Service , Capcom, 475 Oakmead Parkway, Sunnyvale, CA 94085. ****

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children 12 years old and under.  A user who indicates that he or she is 12 years old or younger will not be allowed to register. 

From time to time, certain portions of our websites may allow children under 13 to submit personal information such as their email address without first telling us their age or getting their parent’s permission.  Such portions of our sites operate activities or provide services in a way that does not require prior parental consent under the law.  

We recognize the importance of safeguarding the privacy of children and encourage parents to check and monitor their children's use of online activities regularly. 

Capcom maintains appropriate safeguards that ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the personal information we collect.  Personal information collected by Capcom is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public and that are only accessible by authorized employees.  We also have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control (i.e., maintain data quality).  Before we allow web users to access their personal information, for example, we verify their identity by prompting them to submit information such as their login name and password. 

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding this Privacy Policy or our information collection practices, please contact Capcom by phone at (408) 774-0400, via email at [megamail@capcom.com](mailto:megamail@capcom.com), or by regular mail at: Customer Service , Capcom, 475 Oakmead Parkway , Sunnyvale , CA 94085 .

You can also contact ESRB Privacy Online directly at [www.esrb.org](http://www.esrb.org/) or by regular mail at 317 Madison Avenue, 22nd Floor , New York , NY 10017 . 

_By using a website operated by Capcom_ _USA_ _,_ _you signify your assent to Capcom_ _USA_ _'s Online Privacy Policy.   If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site.  We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy.  Please check back from time to time to ensure that you aware of these changes.  Your continued use of this site will signify your acceptance of these changes.  If we make a material change to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting the change on this website or in this Privacy Policy, and if necessary, give you additional choices regarding such change._

Updated 3/28/05
